Last update: 1/18/2023



Kourosh Ahmadzadeh Ataei

Website | Gmail | Github | Linkedin

Personal Data

Address:

Mashhad, IRAN. Piruzi Blvd., Dehkhoda 7 St., No.226.

Mobile:

+989036928421

Date of birth:

December 19, 1996. (25 years)

About me:

I learned all of my big major of these skills independently although I am **team player** and I willing to **teamwork**. I am **flexible**, **punctual**, **diligent**, **ethical**, **loyal** and **accountable** at work and learn **quickly**. Learning new languages and frameworks enable me to research and develop more and more.

Education

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad (FUM)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering GPA 15.56/20 (3.31 GPA)

Last 2 years GPA is 16.59 (3.52 GPA)

- Mashhad, IRAN Sep. 2016 - Sep. 2021
- Relevant Coursework: Data Mining Algorithm Design Database Information Retrieval -Artificial Intelligence – Web Development - Data communication – Multimedia systems -Data Structures

Areas of Interests

Web development, Rest API, Software engineering, Information Retrieval, Data Mining, Artificial Intelligence.

Experience

Backend Developer

Angizeh Negar Khavaran (Lagrange)

per Jun.2022 – Sep.2022

I am responsible for:

- Develop backend base on python (Fast API)
- Datamining

Main achievement:

- Work in professional team
- Learn and implement structural project

- Work with ORM(SQLAlchemy)
- Work with Airflow
- Participation in datamining Project
- Work with Docker

Junior Software Engineer, Co-Founder Al Trader startup (Aran Accelerator)

Jun. 2021 – Feb. 2022

I am responsible for:

- Develop platform base on python
- Implement telegram bot
- Work with MySQL

- SysAdmin for server side
- Product manager

Main achievement:

- Acquire team management **Teamwork**
- Learn and Implement Pattern Designs

- Some experiences in product manager
- Participation in Al Project

R&D Developer

Green Render Startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

• Configure render farm - multi-GPUs

Main achievement:

- Learn server-side commands and bashscript(ubuntu-centos)
- Work with PostgreSQL
- Learn research and development

Swift Developer Intern

Part software

I am responsible for:

• Develop IOS applications based on swiftand objective-c

Main achievement:

- Learn advance GIT
- Learn swift and IOS development

Jul. 2020 - Oct. 2020

Dec. 2020 - Jun. 2021

Selected Projects

Work

Personal website

Developed a website for my CV & Resumes

- Based on Wordpress
- Include personal blog

Cryptocurrency bot API

Develop an API for cryptocurrency bots

Based on Django rest framework

 App provides selected strategies and auto trading for customers with purchase plans

Learn swift and XCode

• Do tasks and small project

Dec. 2022 – Present

Apr. 2022 - Present

Roomie
 Nov. 2022 – Present

A web application for find roommate

- Based on Django rest framework and react.
- The application fulfills the needs of those who are looking for a roommate with a budget of their choice.

• Data Collection Feb. 2023 – Present

An application that provides a wide range of required data in different formats for those interested.

Based on Django rest framework.

Academic

• Optimization on TF-IDF recommendersystem

Basics of information retrieval and web search, Prof.F.Ensan, FUM.

Fall 2020

 Implemented an optimization on classical TF-IDF algorithm and proposed adaptiveweight of position of word algorithm based on TF-IDF

Network security API

Winter 2019

Fundamentals of Secure Computing, Prof.H.Amintoosi, FUM

 Implemented an API with Django Rest API for check ports, show user logs, Token Authentication System, check available website user requests, DDoS prevention

Charity website

Fall 2019

Principles of Database Design, Prof.B.behkamal, FUM

- Implemented a free food distribution web application for charities and restaurant basedon PHP and MySQL.
- Air Hockey Winter 2016

Advanced Programming, Prof.A.Nouri Baygi, FUM

JavaFx game application with AI agent

Skills

Languages(advance): Python, familiar with SQL, Html, CSS, Java, Swift, bash script

Languages(basic): Java, Solidity, PHP, C

Libraries: NumPy, Pandas, Multithreading, Django, Django REST framework, scrapy, requests

Technologies & Principles: Clean coding & SOLID, OOP, Linux distributions, Git, PyCharm, Google Colab,

MVC, Design Patterns, Scrum, fast API, Telegram bot Languages: English: Upper Intermediate, Persian: Native